boombycindyjoseph.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy | BOOM by Cindy Joseph

Privacy Policy 

**Privacy Policy**  
BOOM! By Cindy Joseph® ("BOOM") is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Website, so we want you to know what information we collect when you visit our site, how we use that information, and how you can update it ("Privacy Policy"). We reserve the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please re-visit this page occasionally to check for updates.

**Information We Collect**  
We collect various types of information from our Website visitors so we can adjust our site to meet our users' needs and expectations. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies and other information is collected if you decide to share information about yourself and your family so we can better keep you informed about new products.

**  
Information Collected Automatically**  
The types of information your browser or Internet session automatically sends us each time you visit our Website, which we automatically collect, include:  
· Your browser.  
· Your computer's operating system.  
· Your navigation path, i.e., the URLs of where you come to our site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as you leave.  
· Your IP address.  
This and other information lets us see how users are finding our Website, and it tells us which pages are visited the most often so we can make our Website more useful.

**Information You Provide to Us**  
In addition to the information automatically collected by your browser, we also collect information that you provide to us when you contact us or order a product such as your name, address, phone number, email address, gender, age, etc.

**How We Use This Information**  
We collect this information that you provide, and may use it to make ordering from our Website easier by pre-populating contact forms with the information that you have provided. We do not share your information with any third-parties unless required by law. We use the information we automatically collect to help us better plan our Website to meet your needs. Information you provide to us is used for marketing purposes, and may result in follow-up communications such as alerts to new products or specials.

**Your Rights and Our Obligations**  
BOOM respects the privacy of users visiting our Website. In addition to our communications to you, we may use certain directory information that we have collected to send you information about products and services, or updates and other information we think may be of interest to you. Please contact us to request your name and address be removed from our lists. If you do not want to receive our e-mail marketing, please submit a request to have your e-mail address removed by emailing: [info@boombycindyjoseph.com.](mailto:info@boombycindyjoseph.com)

**Legal Protections**  
We may disclose information about our users, including your personal information, in the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or other valid law enforcement measures; to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Website and applicable laws; or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of the Website, our users or others. We may also use device identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, internet service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

**Measures to Protect Your Information**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**How "Cookies" Help You**  
When you visit our Website, we may use cookies to keep track of your information. This small piece of program code resides on your computer and stores your contact information for all of our requests for information. We do this so you are not required to re-enter your contact information as you move within our Website. You can generally opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies or warn you before accepting a cookie. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu. However, please be aware that some areas of the Website may not provide you with an acceptable user experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links Provided By BOOM!**  
Our Website may contain links to other websites external to our Website. When you access these external websites, the providers of the websites will have access to certain information about you. BOOM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any websites which we do not directly control.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Protection of Children**  
We do not request personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly accept personally identifiable information from children under that age. If you are under 13 do not use our Website. If we discover that a child under 13 has submitted information to our Website, we will delete this information as soon as possible.

©2010 BOOM! By Cindy Joseph. All Rights Reserved
